Hello friends, today I am very
happy to
make this amazing video in front of you guys, friends, today we will talk about a
very wonderful and amazing daily sales
report for all those
agents who are associated with my team,
whether you are associated with Star Health,
Ta AIA,
Max Life, Apna Ta AAG,
Policy Bazaar, Mant
Pro, IC Lobar
or for any company, you are
already enrolled with me in my team, 35, 400
agents are already working with me on
pan India basis, I have
brought a common single daily sales report for all of them, friends,
such a sales report feedback
form in which it is
most important for all of you to fill it, if friends, you
guys want to make it successful, then you will have to
support me for this and for that, there is
a responsibility which I am going to give you, you have to
genuinely shake hands with this responsibility,
along with that you have to fill it together,
you have to attend every meeting from our place every day  We will take
training and
learn. Whatever message we send you,
you will have to give feedback in every training by giving a small
comment in it. Whenever I or my
team will talk to you, you will have to tell about that team whether the
team is supporting you
or not, whether you are getting help
or not, whether you are
understanding something in the meeting or not, whether you
need any special support or not, whether you
need any special working or not.
I have put all that detailing in this DSR form. Not only this,
I have also
written here that how many policies you have done this month,
you will write that, how much premium you paid this month,
and whether you need any special support there, whether
you have any follow-up going on or
not, whether you are facing any problem,
you need any special support from our side, all that
working is available in it. There are hardly 15 to
20 questions which you have to fill in a very simple
way.
I will also tell you its detailing now,
what all formations are there in it, what all you have to
type quickly. It will hardly take you 5 minutes to
fill this form
but for this  Along with this, there are many
attractive offers in this, in which you will
get a point system and through the point system you will earn many
incentives separately
and due to which you will develop a learning attitude and once you develop a
learning attitude, then friends,
your life will be made, you will rise so much in life
that you would never have imagined,
your earning will be in Apple, you will be in very big
working, I promise you this too,
friends, let's quickly understand
what is this DSR form, in this DSR format,
DSR means Daily Sales Report,
this Daily Sales Report, you have a
googlethalli.com agency came in 2021,
in 2020, you have to select it quickly,
you have fitted it quickly, after this you have to
give us your WhatsApp2 number of today, it happens with some people
that they forget to enter their numbers
or we had only one number, that has been
missed out, then if we have the second number also, then
we will be able to support and
help you, now the next
date will start, whatever meeting you started, whatever
training you have taken through us, after that meeting, go to
this link  You have to fill this or if
you have called from my team or from our team then
also you have to fill this, you will enter today's
date here, after entering the date you will
write whether you joined the meeting today or not,
yes or no and there will be an option in it
what was the topic of today's meeting,
you have to tell the name of the topic, did you understand today's meeting or
not, did you understand a little, did you understand a lot, did
not understand at all, it was
absolutely useless, the training was very good, all those
options are given in it,
just tick, do not write, only
tick,
similarly if you have any extra support or
any extra need, if you have some
such working going on with our team, then please
tell in it, there will be an option for feedback,
what kind of support do you need, similarly if
you have any business follow-up going on or
not, do you have one follow-up, two follow-ups, four
follow-ups, there is not even one, just mention one, two,
five or zero, then write
zero, have you logged in any business till now this month, have you
logged in one policy, two
policies, five policies, number of policies, have
you logged in  If you have to write one then one If you do five
then five If you do 10 then 10
Similarly, how much business have you done, you have to
write the business figure, how much business have you done till now this month, if you have done it then
put it, if you have not done it then put it zero, as simple as that Next, when did
my team call you or
when did you talk to our team, me or
my team Not only this, apart from this, the
next question is whether
you are getting our training messages or not,
you have to answer in yes or no Very very
simple If you are getting them then it is very good If you are not getting them then
I will give you the solution
how will you get them in a month, you have to write
how many trainings you attend within a month
Five trainings
10 trainings 15 trainings 25
trainings
Tentatively, you have to write in the number of trainings you join and
if you do not join more than 10 trainings
in a month then
you have to give a small reason for it like I remain busy, there is
some concern with me or my office
hours are like this  Or whatever your schedule
is, please give the reason why you are
not able to join more than 10 trainings
which you should do. At last but not least,
one or two small questions and the question is, are you
confident or not? Now, have you gained
confidence or not about your company, about the
product and
about its premium calculation? Are you
able to do all these things on your own or not? You have to
answer this in yes or no. And at last but not least, are
you able to create a policy on your own
or not? At last but not least, are you
clear about portability or
not? Do people who sell health insurance know how to do
portability
or not? You have to answer this in yes or no. Are
you aware of the company's ongoing contests, including
monthly contests and quarterly
contests, you have to
write yes or no about that. You have to say yes or no about whether
you know about the company's payout structure
or not.
And last but not least, you have to
share two references with us from any
such agent.  Those who want to join us in this industry,
who want to work in the health insurance
industry, life insurance, motor
insurance or with any company
and you think that there are
two such people in your knowledge, then you have to share their names and
numbers with us. When you share these two
names with us, you will
get 150 points extra for that. You have to do this basic
work, it will hardly take you 5 to 10 minutes.
One,
you have to do the daily sales report,
if you fill this report regularly, you
fill it every day. On the day you
join any training of our team
or have any conversation with our team, on that
day you have to fill this training form DSR form and submit it. So
what will be the benefit of this?
If you
fill the training form on any day,
you will get 100 points for it on daily basis,
100 points for each day. Secondly, if
you have filled that training form for 12 days continuously, then
by doing continuous training for 12 days you will get 200 points
extra. If you get 1200 points  If
yes, then you will get 200 more and it will become 1400.
Similarly, if you have
attended that session for at least 24 days in a month and have
given us feedback in it, then by attending 24 days
you will get 300 points extra,
this will also be an extra special feature
and for three months you will get the same 24-day
working period, if you have
continuously filled that form and
filled the DSR form every month, then
you will get 500 points extra, if
you do this working for 6 months then
you will get 1500 points extra and
if you have logged in two policies in a month, then
you will get 100 points extra by logging in those two policies, you will get
50 points on every policy, you will get 100 points on porting two policies
and in a month if you have
ported any policy,
you will get 100 points on porting till 31 December 2023.
Apart from this, what is the eighth rule,
if you have done two IPAs in a month, then also you will get  You will
get 100 points extra. If you have sold a special plan,
senior citizen plan or any of
your special plans or senior plan, then
you will get 100 points extra on that policy and if you have
sold a 2 year policy, if you have sold a two year
policy then you will get 150 points
extra and if you have a 3 year policy
together then you will get 300 points
extra. This is the total. If you have
sold any OPD plan also then
you will get 100 points extra.
What will be the point system of this, see, I
explained the point system that these points will be given,
our team will calculate it, we will
make it successful, it is your job,
you have to fill this DSR form regularly,
how big is its benefit, I will
explain it to you here, if you fill it then
what benefits will you get from it,
friends, we have kept 10 slabs in this, right now I will
explain to you, on which day you
redeem it or not, it will be in your hands, on
which day also you
give the gift of WhatsApp2, then we will
transfer it to you on the same day and those
points will become zero.  Let me explain the first slab,
what will you get,
what will you get for how many points, the
first slab is if you get 1500
points, you can get
1500 points at any time, we will make your ID card and provide you
a good
executive diary printed in your name, the
first slab is of
1500 points which is very simple, it will be done
in 10, 12, 15 days, second if you have
3000 points,
then we will
also make your youtube2 visiting card,
we will do both the work for you on 3000 points, we will get
1000 visiting cards printed in your name
and along with
youtube3 slab, if you get 5000 points, then for
5000 points, that
youtube3 video in your name, your photo will be
uploaded from your email id in which
I will have explained the plan and
you will do its marketing and you will get its benefits,
along with that marketing tool will also be
given through which  You can generate huge leads by promoting it extensively.
We will also tell you all those options. If you do
not want this option, then in return you
can redeem it for ₹5000000 [Music] cash. You
can choose any one of the three options.
As soon as you get 7000 points, then for 7000
points we will upload a pack of five videos for
you in
which I will have explained the plan, the
working will be mine, the name, number, video,
everything will be yours and not only this, if
you do not want this then we will give you a digital
watch which you call a smart watch, we will
provide it to you or we will give you a
cash reward. You can choose any of these three.
This is your 10000
points. As soon as you get 10000 points, you will
get an opportunity.
Either take that or apart from that, buy a
good quality bun china
dinner set or
13000 points for ₹2000000 points  As soon as there are 13000
points, here we have kept ₹1 cash
and there is a pack of 15 videos which you can
take on YouTube. There are 16000 points.
In 16000 points, there is ₹1 cash. If there are
2000 points, then ₹77000 cash. If there are 25000
points, then 8100 cash and if
you make 30000 points, then you
can get ₹1000000 cash reward from us.
We have created a very amazing point system
in the DSR module. Look friends, this is the
digital era and in this digital era, you will have to be
responsible yourself, for which
you have to fill and update this DSR form on a daily basis by spending very simple 5 to 10 minutes
and after submitting it, you have to
share it with your sales manager that
I have sent today's report. You will do this work every day. The
report will be acceptable only once in a day and
more than once.  It will
not be allowed. If you
fill four, five or ten forms repeatedly in a single day, then it will not be allowed.
Keep in mind that you have to submit it only once every day
and
send its screenshot only once. So friends, this is very
amazing, it is generally useful for you.
Please make it successful because
you are going to benefit a lot from it. I will
tell you its benefit,
what will be the benefit for you by giving such feedback. Suppose you
filled this form for 15 days, 20 days, 25 days. By filling it,
I will understand
how many trainings you joined in a month,
which trainings you understood,
which trainings you did not understand, which
follow-ups are available to you, how much
business you did, how much business you did not do, are
you getting support from our team or
not? My team is calling you to check whether
you need any general help, whether you need
special working, whether you got that
working or not, I will be
able to check from the Excel sheet with a single click that
Ram Kumar, Vijay Kumar, Ajay Kumar,
Shyam Shyamlal  Yes, what requirement has been
asked from my team which my team did
not fulfill? If you have any concern or problem,
you can highlight that too,
I will provide the option for that as well. If you have any suggestion,
any support, any big problem for
which you are not getting a solution,
you will get the comment option at the end, you will
feed it in that and my team or I will be alerted
that you should get this solution, whether it is a problem
regarding a claim, or a
problem regarding payout, or
any kind of correction or support, if you have a
problem with anything, you can mention it in the last option in the
suggestion option, in the complaint option.
Friends,
by pressing that button I will be
able to check on every person personally. So friends, this
Jannali makes this report
difficult for 3 days on Google, after that it makes it very
easy, it helps a lot.
Jannali will be very useful for you,
trust me once, you have to make this DSF form
successful, you have to make it successful
and if you do this then I will be grateful to you for the rest of my life
and in this you will see our
quality  There will be a huge change, a huge
working will come out,
please cooperate, please support, this is
genuinely for you, thank you so much.